

□ (+60) 14-881-7836 | **>** byu1628@protonmail.com | **□** gohanko | **□** gohanko

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

### **Summary**

Building software for the web — experienced in the Javascript and Python ecosystem.

### Skills

**Languages** Javascript, Python, Perl5

**Tooling** Git, Bash, Linux, Mobx, Lerna, grunt/gulp, npm/yarn

Frameworks React, Hapi, Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, Scrapy, Microsoft SQL Server, PostgreSQL

**Industry Knowledge** CI/CD, Agile Software Development

## Work Experience

#### **Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Cyberjaya, Malaysia

Dec. 2018 - Dec. 2020

Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2018

- Learned and adopted new technology quickly (Javascript/Perl5).
- Use React, Grunt, Mobx, Webpack and SASS to build and maintain frontend applications.
- Implement a chat application by integrating SendBird's chat API.
- Coordinate with UI/UX to implement designs for our web applications using tools such as Abstract, Zeplin and Invision.
- Collaborated with compliance to make sure our software complies with the laws.
- Use NodeJS, Docker, and PostgreSQL to build server side services for automating payments.
- Participated in typical software development process such as sprint meetings, and code reviews.
- Autonomously outline work and set backlog along with prioritization.
- Help our recruitment team with proctoring new tech candidates in our hackathon.

**Freelance** Remote

SOFTWARE ENGINEER • Use Django, and Django Rest Framework to build a REST API for an over-the-counter payment tracking service.

· Collaborated with project managers, company owners and other engineers over the internet to work on projects requested.

# Projects\_\_\_\_\_

### Jenexus Invoice Management System

Remote

**BACKEND DEVELOPER** 

Jun. 2017 - Aug. 2017

- · Contracted to build the backend for an invoice management system by a software house for their client.
- In summary, it is a basic CRUD app built using Django, complete with unit tests and documentation.
- There were about 16 views/pages which does various stuff but essentially boils down to CRUD.
- · Business logic is written primarily in these views, and models are kept strictly for data queries and data manipulation.
- · Tests are written using unittests which tests the views by checking its return values (status code, content in page, etc), tests are also written for models to check if our custom functions are returning the correct values.
- Deployed on an Ubuntu instance (Debian is also tested). This involved a lot of manual setup but in hindsight we could have use Docker and written scripts to automate the deployment as well as data backups. CI/CD would have been nice as well.

### Education

#### **Riam Road Secondary School**

Miri, Malaysia

MALAYSIAN CERTIFICATE OF EXAMINATION

Jan. 2014 - Dec. 2016

- The Malaysian Certificate of Examination is the equivalent of the GCSE in England or GCE Ordinary Level in the Commonwealth of Nations.
- Scored a 3A 4B in the examination which includes Mathematics (A-), Science (A), English (A), Malay (B+), Moral Studies (B+), History (B), and Art (B+).
- The English subject has 2 results, one is the MCE result and the other is the GCE Ordinary Level result, in which I scored an A as well.